[TALIA] Well, your plan worked.
Because of you, Ms. Talia.
[BILLY] There's only one thing
you need to know, Ms. Talia.
You can't trust Bea Mercado.
We hit the jackpot with this!
But more importantly,
it will be a big blow to Billy.
Good thing she took the bait.
Thank you.
Billy, anything for you.
I can't believe she didn't involve us
in the plan.
It would have been risky
if she'd told us the plan, right?
But still, it's a shame, isn't it?
I mean, imagine the suspense
and the contents we could have
made out of it, right?
[JORDAN] ♪ Even in the silence ♪
♪ You're the only one
On my mind ♪
♪ Can we take a rest? ♪
♪ I might say something I'll regret ♪
♪ Baby, I won't be long ♪
♪ I'll be back by the end of the song ♪
[BEA] Please.
Please, I'm begging you.
Do you know I'm getting
in trouble because of you?
Just leave me alone.
Because they think we're accomplices.
I could even go to jail because of you.
So please, I'm begging you.
Please, please. Stay away from me.
[LAUGHING]
Accomplices?! You got that right!
We're accomplices!
Accomplices in love, right?
- Crazy! You're crazy!
- [CALOY] That's how, right?
[BEA] Ma'am, you see?
I had nothing to do with him!
He's totally out of his mind.
I never asked him to do anything
because I don't even know him!
[EVENT MC] Please join me as we celebrate
one of today's
Young Entrepreneurial awardees,
Ms. Benilda Cariño.
[BILLY] A few years ago,
my friends and I were just talking about
love.
And from those honest
late-night conversations,
LoveList was born.
LoveList stands where it is today
because of my team,
my best friend,
my LoveList family,
and my family.
I promise, from here on,
it only gets better.
Because every Filipina
deserves to feel safe
and empowered in love.
Again, thank you very much.
[APPLAUSE]
Dude, cheers to you
and to your genius plan.
Genius!
Congrats to us.
- Thank you.
- [JORDAN] And now…
Caloy's behind bars.
One problem solved.
Cheers!
And cheers to your acting too!
Because you're the best actor.
You really nailed it earlier.
Of course. You know how talented I am.
Mm! You really are!
Did you see earlier?
After your performance,
so many women came up to you.
They were handing you their calling cards.
I don't know if those were offers
for gigs or dates.
Which were they?
Both. Duh!
Wow, you really are so talented!
- Cheers to that.
- [BOTTLES CLINK]
[BILLY CHUCKLES]
[WOMAN SINGING IN BACKGROUND]
[PEOPLE APPLAUDING]
Oh, it's your turn. Do you want to--
You should perform.
- Let's both do it.
- They're done.
Wanna do it?
Thank you.
[PEOPLE APPLAUDING]
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
So annoying. I said I don't feel like it!
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
[MUSIC ENDS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- Oh. Billy.
- Hi, Auntie Pres.
- You came home?
- Mm-hmm.
Why didn't you just stay
at the hotel overnight?
- What a waste.
- No, it's fine.
You could've just
spent time with your friends.
[BILLY] It's okay.
With the amount of stress
you're dealing with,
you deserve to let off some steam
and have fun.
You know, Auntie Pres,
my real stress-relievers
are you and Oliver.
Knowing that you're both safe
makes me happy.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Good night.
- Good night.
- Huh?
Go to sleep, please.
[PRECIOUS CHUCKLES]
- [MUSIC FADES]
- [ENRICO SIGHS]
Enrico.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Well?
It's way past your 10-day deadline
with Boss Zandro.
Where's the payment?
I've sent Zandro 20,000 pesos.
Twenty thousand pesos?
Are you stupid?
You owe him 20,000 dollars.
I'll pay in full
next month.
Do you think I'm an idiot? Huh?
You think I was just bluffing
with my threat?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[THUG GROANS]
- [PANTING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PANICKED SHOUTS]
Help!
Let's take him to the hospital!
Sir, are you okay?
Oliver, put that away, please.
It's mealtime.
Okay.
Who are you chatting with?
Biboy.
He's asking to come with me
and Suzie to study.
Oh, really?
You've made up?
Mm-hmm. Sir Eric made them
patch things up.
- [BAG ZIPS]
- Hmm.
He's become nicer to me.
Has he really?
Or is he just scared of Sir Eric?
Mm!
But that's good.
I should give my thanks to that Sir Eric.
Mm-hmm. That's right. You really should.
He's such a nice guy, if you meet him.
- Auntie Pres…
- It's true.
What if you go there today to meet him?
Today?
Oh, I can't. I have a breakfast meeting.
Sorry. I'll try to go at lunchtime.
- Are you sure?
- Yes. I'll try.
- I'll hold you to that.
- Yes.
[PRECIOUS] Okay.
Oliver, can you stop chatting
during meals, please?
- Put that away.
- Mm!
And finish your breakfast.
I'm taking you to school.
But don't worry,
this will be the last time.
You won't have a chaperone
starting next week.
But it's okay.
It's fine that you're always at school.
I'm an Auntie's boy anyway,
and a Billy's boy.
- What a flatterer.
- That won't work on us.
- We know you'd love that.
- You're smooth-talking us.
- Okay, enough with that.
- Turn it off.
I'll take this.
- [PRECIOUS] Enough.
- Keep eating now.
I'll pack your lunch.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, so for full verification,
we'll need backend access to your system.
It's for real-time ID check
and fraud monitoring.
Yes, but only limited API access.
We can't grant you direct access
to our main database.
Sensitive data must be encrypted with us.
This makes it safer for our users.
Okay. Will it be possible to do
in eight weeks?
Six weeks.
We already have a framework.
We just have to do the integration.
Very confident, Mr. Valentin.
Confidence is preparation.
Then we have a deal.
- Sir Andy, thank you.
- Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Okay. Thank you. I'll go ahead.
- Yes. We'll see you soon. Thank you.
- Take care.
[MUSIC FADES]
Six weeks?
You sure about that, dude?
You don't trust me? That's basic!
Not really. [CLICKS TONGUE]
[CHUCKLES] Is that so?
- Fine. Ten weeks.
- Oh, I take it back!
Thank you. Thank you.
Gosh, what would I do
if I didn't have
my ridiculously cocky best friend?
Mm!
He's talented, handsome, and smells good!
He's perfect!
All he's missing is a girlfriend.
We'll find one for him. Mm!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop flattering me.
I'm the only one
you'll hear that from, you know.
By the way,
I'm going to Oliver's school.
I want to meet that Eric guy
they always talk about
so I can thank him.
Okay, I'm coming with you.
- Okay.
- [PHONE RINGING]
Here's your cake, ma'am.
Hello? Thank you.
[WOMAN] May I speak with Benilda Cariño?
Speaking. Who's this?
Ma'am, this is Nurse Anj
from St. John Hospital.
You're listed as an emergency contact.
Emergency contact for whom?
Oliver?
For patient Enrico Dominguez.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BILLY] Why?
What happened to him?
I'll take a look first if you want.
It's okay.
Miss, what room is Enrico Dominguez in?
What's your relationship with the patient?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
He's my father.
He's in Bed 3.
- Thank you.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you a relative?
[ECG MONITOR BEEPING]
Yes, boss.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
He's still unconscious,
but his vitals are stable.
We'll keep him under observation
for the next 24 hours.
It's important that
we monitor him closely tonight.
Okay, Doc.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
So his blood sugar just dropped.
He'll be fine.
Awesome, isn't it?
Of all the things he could've
passed down to my brother,
it just had to be diabetes.
Miss, how much is the bill
for Enrico Dominguez?
- [CASHIER] One moment, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Here, ma'am.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[BILLY] What?
I thought you didn't care about your dad?
I don't.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Auntie, I'm so excited for Billy
to finally meet Sir Eric.
Me too. I'm sure your sister's
also going to like him.
You too? You mean you like…?
Hey, cut it out! It's not like that.
I'm okay with it, Auntie.
I think you and Sir Eric
make a better couple
than you and Coach Brandon.
What are you talking about?
You're too young to be thinking
about things like that.
I didn't just come up with it.
I see it.
You get way more excited around him
than you did with Coach Brandon.
- What?!
- [BOTH LAUGH]
- Oh.
- [LUCY] Hi.
Good morning.
Is Sir Eric here?
He won't be coming in today.
Just a moment.
[WHINING]
Auntie won't get to see Sir Eric.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
- She's sad now. [LAUGHS]
- Huh? No way!
Cut it out! Someone might hear you.
Too bad.
I can't believe he put me down
as his emergency contact.
What was he expecting?
Well, I think you did exactly
what he expected you to do.
What?
You went to see him.
You even paid his bill.
As if you still care.
Dude, he listed me
as his emergency contact.
Of course I had to pay for it. Otherwise,
the hospital might come after me later.
[MAN] So you're Enrico's daughter?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you want?
Your father owes my boss
a huge sum of money.
Over a million pesos.
Okay.
Okay? It isn't okay!
He needs to pay it back.
It's his debt, not mine.
He doesn't have the money to pay it back.
Then he shouldn't have borrowed
the money in the first place.
And your boss
shouldn't have lent it to him.
Wait a minute.
- Hey!
- Jordan!
- That's your problem!
My friend has nothing to do with it, okay?
- Come on, let's just go.
- Okay?!
- That's enough! Jordan!
- Let go!
We have nothing to do with his debt.
Please, leave us alone.
Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS MOROSE]
- [SIGHS] No…
- [PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hey.
I just called to check if you're okay.
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
How could I not?
Look.
I just thought you should know.
I'm at the police station.
What? What are you doing there?
I don't want to add to your problems,
but I'm sure sooner or later,
you'll find out anyway.
[JORDAN] I just found out
Bea got off the hook again.
Caloy denies that they were accomplices.
What?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Bea abandoned you.
Why are you still protecting her?
I did it on my own.
But why did you target Billy?
Why?!
Your father really is the worst.
He even got you involved in his debts.
I already knew that
he was only after money.
What if he comes back?
He might get the wrong idea
and think that you care about him.
[VALERIE] You should've also mentioned
his partner-in-crime, Bea Mercado.
And we'll let the world know
that she's also a criminal.
[VALERIE] Yeah.
Can you please talk to your people?
Maybe they want to know
what a real criminal is.
Do you think you're going to scare me?
Enjoy your freedom
because it won't last long.
Ralph's mom sent this.
And now, they're questioning me
if they did the right thing
when they invested in us.
I tried to ask
what the real reason is for all of this.
If it's just for money.
It's not about money.
If it were, they would've asked
for some a long time ago.